favable.com 2013-03-28

# FAVable - Web application for managing bookmarks - Web service for managing favorite websites.

At FAVable, we respect the privacy of the users of our website and services and are committed to protecting it. We have created this policy to demonstrate our commitment to you and to help you understand it. nformation collected by FAVable will continue to be subject to the FAVable privacy policy, posted here.

We may collect personal information, including email addresses, when individuals register to use the FAVable website and services, post a link to the FAVable website or submit questions, submit bookmarks, comments or bug reports. We may also, at times, collect our users' IP addresses and information regarding our users' use of our website and services. We may use such IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our servers, track movement within our website and, if necessary, deny service in accordance with our Terms of Service. We may also collect information related to the referring URL, access times and browser type. Unless required by law, we will not share our users' personal information, Internet Protocol (IP) addresses and usage information, except with their consent or in aggregate or anonymous form, with third parties.

In order to offer and provide optimized and personalized services, we use cookies to store and sometimes track information about our users. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to a user's browser from a web server and is eventually stored on a user's computer hard drive.

Google uses web beacons to research certain usage and activities of the Google and FAVable web sites. The information collected through these web beacons is used to find out more about our users, for more accurate reporting, improve the effectiveness of our marketing, and to make FAVable better. No personally identifiable information from your FAVable account is collected using these web beacons.

Our services give you the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. We will never automatically send you information/offers you do not want. You must choose to receive them.

Visit your FAVable Settings to edit your profile and other information. When you're signed in, FAVable page headers will include a link to Settings. You can delete your FAVable account through your Settings.

FAVable reserves the right to modify all or some of this Privacy Policy at any time without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post a notice on our website so our users are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will use information only in accordance with the Privacy Policy under which the information was collected unless we have received explicit authorization from the appropriate user(s) to do otherwise.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this website or your dealings with this FAVable, you can send an e-mail, in English, to [support@favable.com](mailto:support@favable.com).

Effective Date: January 18, 2011
